I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
But dying in the place
of someone I love
seems like a good way to go.
So I can't bring myself
to regret the decision
to leave home.
I would miss Phoenix.
I'd miss the heat.
I would miss my loving,
erratic, harebrained mother.
Okay.
Renee, come on.
And her new husband.
Guys, come on.
I love you both.
We got a plane to catch.
But they want to
go on the road,
so I'm gonna spend
some time with my dad,
and this will be
a good thing.
I think.
♪ When the thorn bush
turns white
♪ That's when I'll come home
♪ I am going out to
see what I can sow
♪ And I don't know
where I'll go
what I'll see
In the state of Washington,
under a near constant cover
of clouds and rain,
there's a small town
named Forks.
Population, 3,120 people.
This is where I'm moving.
My dad's Charlie.
He's the chief of police.
♪ Curse the powers that be
♪ Cause all I want is... ♪
Your hair's longer.
I cut it since
the last time
I saw you.
Guess it grew out again.
I used to
spend two weeks here
almost every summer,
but it's been years.
I've cleared
some shelves off
in the bathroom.
Right. One bathroom.
It's a pretty
good work lamp.
The sales lady
picked out
the bed stuff.
You like purple, right?
Purple's cool.
Thanks.
Okay.
One of the best
things about Charlie,
he doesn't hover.
Heard you guys coming
all the way down the road.
Good to see you.
Bella, you remember
Billy Black.
Yeah.
Wow, you're looking good.
Well, I'm still dancing.
I'm glad you're finally here.
Charlie here hasn't shut up
about it since you told him
you were coming.
All right, keep exaggerating.
I'll roll you into the mud.
After I ram you
in the ankles.
You want to go?
Yeah.
Bring it.
Hi, I'm Jacob.
Hey.
We used to make mud pies
when we were little.
Right. No, I remember.
Are they always like this?
It's getting worse
with old age.
Good.
So, what do you think?
Of what?
Your homecoming present.
This?
Just bought it
off Billy here.
Yep.
I totally rebuilt
the engine for you.
Come on.
Oh, my gosh!
This is perfect.
Are you joking me?
Sorry.
I told you she'd love it.
I'm down with the kids.
Oh, yeah, dude.
You're the bomb.
Okay.
Listen,
you gotta double-pump
the clutch when you shift,
but besides that,
you should be good.
That's this one?
Yeah. Yeah, right there.
All right.
Do you want a ride to
school or something?
I go to school
on the reservation.
Right, right.
Yeah.
That's too bad.
It would've been nice
to know one person.
My first day
at a new school.
It's March,
middle of the semester.
Great.
Nice ride.
Thanks.
Good one.
You're Isabella Swan,
the new girl.
Hi, I'm Eric,
the eyes and ears
of this place.
Anything you need,
tour guide, lunch date,
shoulder to cry on?
I'm really kind of the more
suffer-in-silence type.
Good headline
for your feature.
I'm on the paper,
and you're news,
baby, front page.
No, I'm not.
You...
Please don't
have any sort of...
Chillax. No feature.
Okay, thanks.
Cool?
All right. Okay. Yeah.
Get it! Get it! Get it!
To you!
Whoa!
I'm sorry.
I told them not
to let me play.
No way. No, no, no.
That's... That's... Don't...
You're Isabella, right?
Just Bella.
Yeah. Hey, I'm Mike Newton.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, yeah.
She's got
a great spike, huh?
Yeah, it's...
I'm Jessica, by the way.
Hey, you're from
Arizona, right?
Yeah.
Aren't people from Arizona
supposed to be, like,
really tan?
Yeah.
Maybe that's why
they kicked me out.
You're good.
That's so funny.
Back in, Jess.
Down here.
Like a masterpiece,
you know,
we'll have, like,
this crazy pyramid
fall from the sky,
and then
you guys can...
It's my pleasure, Madame.
You guys can give
each other high fives.
Burrito, my friend?
Hey, Mikey! You met
my home girl, Bella?
Hey.
Your home girl?
Yeah.
Yeah?
That's...
My girl.
Sorry I had to mess
up your game, Mike!
Tyler.
Yes!
Oh, my God.
It's like first grade
all over again.
You're the shiny new toy.
Smile.
Okay.
Sorry.
I needed a candid
for the feature.
The feature's dead,
Angela.
Don't bring it
up again.
It's okay, I just...
I got your back, baby.
Guess we'll just run
another editorial
on teen drinking.
You know,
you can always go
for eating disorders.
Speedo padding
on the swim team.
Actually, that's a good one.
Kirk. Right? That's
exactly what I thought.
Yeah.
We're talking Olympic-size.
There's no way.
He's so skinny.
It doesn't make sense.
Totally.
Yeah.
Who are they?
The Cullens.
They're Dr. and Mrs.
Cullen's foster kids.
They moved down here
from Alaska, like,
a few years ago.
They kind of
keep to themselves.
Yeah, 'cause
they're all together.
Like, together, together.
The blonde girl,
that's Rosalie,
and the big
dark-haired guy, Emmett,
they're, like, a thing.
I'm not even sure
that's legal.
Jess, they're not
actually related.
Yeah, but they
live together.
It's weird.
And, okay, the little
dark-haired girl's Alice.
She's really weird,
and she's with Jasper,
the blond one who looks
like he's in pain.
Dr. Cullen's like this
foster dad/matchmaker.
Maybe he'll adopt me.
Who's he?
That's Edward Cullen.
He's totally gorgeous,
obviously,
but apparently
nobody here's
good enough for him.
Like I care, you know?
So, yeah.
Seriously, like,
don't waste your time.
I wasn't planning on it.
Mr. Molina.
Hey, Mike.
Oh, yes. Miss Swan.
Hi. Can I have the pass?
Thank you.
Welcome to the class. Here.
Here's your stuff, okay?
And I got a seat
for you right here,
so come over.
The last one.
Just follow along
till you catch up.
All right, guys, today
we are gonna be observing
the behavior of planaria,
aka flatworms.
So what we're gonna do...
...regenerate.
Zombie worms.
No cell phones.
Guys, let's get to it.
Gentle, gentle,
certain areas.
Please just don't cut here.
We don't cut here.
You won't believe this.
Let's try to focus
while we check
those out, huh, guys?
There must be
something open.
Physics? Biochem?
No, every class is full.
Just a minute, dear.
I'm afraid you'll
have to stay in biology.
Fine. Just...
I'll just have to
endure it.
I just can't get over
how grown up you are.
And so gorgeous.
Hey, Bella.
You remember me?
I played Santa one year.
Yeah, Waylon,
she hasn't had a Christmas
here since she was four.
I bet I made an impression,
though, didn't I?
You always do.
Butt-crack Santa?
Hey, kids love those
little bottles, though.
All right, let the girl eat
her garden burger, Waylon.
As soon as you're done,
I will bring you
your favorite.
Berry cobbler, remember?
Your dad still has it.
Every Thursday.
Thank you.
That'd be great.
Here.
Thanks.
Hey, baby. So, listen,
if spring training goes well,
we could be moving to Florida.
Please insert $1.25
for an additional
three minutes.
Mom, where's your cell?
Okay, don't laugh.
I didn't lose
my power cord.
It ran away.
Screaming. I literally
repel technology now.
I miss you.
Oh, baby, I miss you, too.
But tell me more
about your school.
Now, what are the kids like?
Are there any cute guys?
Are they being nice to you?
Well,
they're all very welcoming.
Tell me all about it.
It doesn't even matter.
Yes, it does, honey.
I have homework to do.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay. I love you.
Love you, too.
I planned to confront him
and demand to know
what his problem was.
But he never showed.
Bella!
And the next day,
another no-show.
More days passed.
Things were getting
a little strange.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
Ice doesn't really help
the uncoordinated.
Yeah. That's why
I had some new tires
put on the truck.
Old ones were
getting pretty bald.
Well, probably
be late for dinner.
I gotta head down
to Mason County.
Security guard
at the Grisham Mill
got killed by
some kind of animal.
An animal?
You're not in
Phoenix anymore, Bells.
Anyway,
I figured I'd lend a hand.
Be careful.
Always am.
And thanks for the tires.
Yeah.
Prom Committee
is a chick thing,
but I gotta cover it
for the paper anyway,
and they need a guy
to help choose the music,
so I need your play list.
Hey, listen, I was wondering,
did you have a date to...
What's up, Arizona? Huh?
How you liking
the rain, girl?
Better get used
to it, girl.
Yeah, Mike, hey,
you're real cute, man.
Oh, I know...
That was really awesome.
Why you shooting down
my game? Let a playa play.
Yeah, okay.
What you playing at,
T-Ball?
Hello.
I'm sorry,
I didn't get a chance to
introduce myself last week.
I'm Edward Cullen.
You're Bella?
Yes.
Onion root tip cells,
that's what's on
your slides right now.
Okay?
So, separate and label them
into the phases of mitosis,
and the first partners
that get it right
are gonna win
the Golden Onion.
All right, good.
Ladies first.
You were gone.
Yeah.
I was out of town
for a couple of days.
Personal reasons.
Prophase.
Do you mind if I look?
It's prophase.
Like I said.
So are you enjoying
the rain?
What?
You're asking me
about the weather?
Yeah, I...
I guess I am.
Well, I don't
really like the rain.
Any cold, wet thing,
I don't really...
What?
Nothing.
It's anaphase.
You mind if I check?
Sure.
Anaphase.
Like I said.
If you hate the cold
and the rain so much,
why'd you move to
the wettest place
in the continental US?
It's complicated.
I'm sure I can keep up.
My mom remarried, and...
So you don't
like the guy, or...
No, that's not...
Phil's really nice.
It's metaphase.
You want to check it?
I believe you.
Why didn't you move
with your mother and Phil?
Well,
Phil's a minor league
baseball player,
and he travels a lot,
and my mom
stayed home with me,
but I knew
it made her unhappy,
so I figured I'd stay
with my dad for a while.
And now you're unhappy.
No.
I'm sorry, I'm just...
I'm just trying
to figure you out.
You're very difficult
for me to read.
Hey, did you get contacts?
No.
Your eyes were black
the last time I saw you,
and now they're,
like, golden brown.
Yeah, I know, it's the...
It's the fluorescents.
Bella!
Dial 911!
I already called.
They're gonna send
somebody over soon.
Bella, I'm so sorry.
I panicked.
Bella, I've got 911
on the phone now.
Bella. You okay?
You and I are gonna talk.
You all right?
I'm fine, Dad. Calm down.
I'm sorry, Bella.
I tried to stop.
I know. It's okay.
No.
It sure as hell
is not okay.
Dad, it wasn't his fault.
You could've been killed.
You understand that?
Yes. But I wasn't, so...
You can kiss your
license goodbye.
I heard the chief's
daughter was here.
Dr. Cullen.
Charlie.
I've got this one,
Jackie.
Isabella.
Bella.
Well, Bella, looks like
you took quite a spill.
How do you feel?
Good.
Look here.
You might experience some
post-traumatic stress
or disorientation,
but your vitals look good.
No signs of any head trauma.
I think you'll be just fine.
I'm so sorry, Bella.
I'm really...
You know,
it would've been
a whole lot worse
if Edward wasn't there.
He knocked me
out of the way.
Edward? Your boy?
Yeah, it was amazing.
I mean,
he got to me so fast.
He was nowhere near me.
Sounds like you
were very lucky.
Charlie.
I gotta go sign
some paperwork.
You should...
You should probably
call your mom.
Did you tell her?
She's probably just
freaking out.
...fifteen kids that
saw what happened.
What was I
supposed to do, then?
Let her die?
This isn't just about you.
It's about all of us.
I think we should
take this in my office.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
Rosalie.
What?
How did you get over
to me so fast?
I was standing right
next to you, Bella.
No. You were
next to your car,
across the lot.
No, I wasn't.
Yes, you were.
Bella, you're...
You hit your head.
I think you're confused.
I know what I saw.
And what exactly was that?
You...
You stopped the van.
You pushed it away
with your hand.
Well, nobody's
gonna believe you, so...
I wasn't gonna
tell anybody.
I just need to
know the truth.
Can't you just thank me
and get over it?
Thank you.
You're not gonna
let this go, are you?
No.
Well, then I hope you
enjoy disappointment.
And that was the first night
I dreamt of Edward Cullen.
I need everybody's
permission slips, okay?
Sammy, please collect them.
Yeah.
Guys, let's go.
Come on, get in.
In. Let's go!
Look at you, huh?
You're alive.
I know, yeah.
False alarm, I guess.
Yeah.
Now, I wanted to ask you,
you know, if, you know,
it's like
a month away, but...
Do you wanna go
to prom with me?
So, what do you think?
About what?
Do you want to go?
To prom?
With me?
Prom.
Dancing.
Not such a good idea for me.
I have something
that weekend anyway.
I'm going to Jacksonville
that weekend.
You can't go another weekend?
Non-refundable ticket.
You should ask Jessica.
I know she wants
to go with you.
All right. All right.
Yo, yo, yo.
Hey, guys, come on.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Green is what? Good.
Let's go. Guys, come on.
Other bus, other bus.
Let's go.
Egg shells, carrot tops.
Compost is cool.
Now, stuff that
in there, Eric.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Very good, very good.
Now, I am gonna
make a steaming cup
of compost tea.
Okay.
Give me that.
Yeah. This is recycling
in its most basic form, guys.
Don't drink it!
It's for the plants.
What's in Jacksonville?
How did you
know about that?
You didn't
answer my question.
You don't answer
any of mine, so...
I mean,
you don't even
say hi to me.
Hi.
Are you gonna tell me
how you stopped the van?
Yeah. I had
an adrenaline rush.
It's very common.
You can Google it.
Floridians.
That's what's
in Jacksonville.
Can you at least
watch where you walk?
Look, I'm sorry
I'm being rude
all the time.
I just think
it's the best way.
Bella! Guess who
just asked me to prom.
Who?
Yeah,
I actually totally thought
that Mike was gonna ask you.
It's not gonna be weird,
though, right?
No. Zero weirdness.
You guys
are great together.
I know, right?
Tyler...
Gross.
Bella, look. It's a worm.
It's a worm.
Bella,
we shouldn't be friends.
You really should've figured
that out a little earlier.
I mean,
why didn't you just
let the van crush me
and save yourself
all this regret?
What, you think
I regret saving you?
I can see that you do.
I just... I don't know why.
You don't know anything.
Hi.
Are you gonna be
riding with us?
No, our bus is full.
Your mom called. Again.
Well, that's your fault.
You shouldn't have told her
about the "almost" accident.
You finished?
Yeah.
Yeah, I suppose you're right.
She always did know
how to worry.
She seems different.
She seems happy.
Phil sounds like
an all right guy.
Yeah, he is.
All right.
No, you need the mitts.
You need them.
No, why do you
keep arguing with me?
You just need them.
You're gonna get frostbite!
I don't even know.
Yeah. Hey!
La Push, baby. You in?
Should I know
what that means?
La Push Beach down
at the Quileute Rez.
We're all going tomorrow.
Yeah, there's a big
swell coming in.
And I don't just
surf the Internet.
Eric, you stood up once,
and it was a foam board.
But there's
whale watching, too.
Come with us.
La Push, baby. It's La Push.
Okay, I'll go if you
stop saying that, okay?
Seriously, dude.
It's creepy, man.
What?
That's what it's called.
So...
Edible art?
Bella.
Thanks.
You know, your mood swings are
kind of giving me whiplash.
I only said it'd be better
if we weren't friends,
not that I didn't wanna be.
What does that mean?
It means if you were smart,
you'd stay away from me.
Okay, well, let's say
for argument's sake
that I'm not smart.
Would you tell me the truth?
No, probably not.
I'd rather hear
your theories.
I have considered
radioactive spiders
and Kryptonite.
That's all superhero
stuff, right?
What if I'm not the hero?
What if I'm the bad guy?
You're not.
I can see what
you're trying to put off,
but I can see that
it's just to keep
people away from you.
It's a mask.
Why don't we just hang out?
Everybody's going
to the beach.
Come.
I mean, have fun.
Which beach?
La Push.
I don't know.
I just...
Is there something wrong
with that beach?
It's just a little crowded.
Hey, it's freezing.
I'm paddling out, Coates.
I don't know if
it's worth it anymore.
We drove all
the way out here.
I'm at least
paddling out.
Yeah.
She's right.
You guys are babies.
So, I keep thinking
that Eric's gonna
ask me to the prom,
and then he just doesn't.
You should ask him.
Take control.
You're a strong,
independent woman.
I am?
Yes.
Hey, will you do me up?
Yeah.
Bella!
Hi, Jacob.
Guys, this is Jacob.
Hey, guys. How you doing?
Hi.
What are you, like,
stalking me?
You're on my rez,
remember?
Are you surfing?
Definitely not.
Thanks.
You guys should
keep Bella company.
Her date bailed.
What date?
She invited Edward.
To be polite, that's it.
I think it's nice
she invited him.
Nobody ever does.
Yeah,
'cause Cullen's a freak.
You got that right.
You guys know him?
The Cullens
don't come here.
What did your friends
mean about, you know,
"The Cullens don't come here?"
You caught that, huh?
I'm not really supposed
to say anything about it.
Hey, I can keep a secret.
Really, it's just like
an old scary story.
Well, I want to know.
Okay, did you know
Quileutes are supposedly
descended from wolves?
What? Like, wolves?
Yeah.
Like, real wolves?
Well, that's
the legend of our tribe.
Okay.
So what's the story
about the Cullens?
Well, they're supposedly
descended from this,
like, enemy clan.
My great grandfather,
the chief,
found them hunting
on our land.
But they claimed to be
something different,
so we made a treaty
with them.
If they promised to
stay off Quileute lands,
then we wouldn't expose
what they really were
to the palefaces.
I thought they
just moved here.
Or just moved back.
Right.
It touched my hand.
A snake! Stop!
Well, what are they really?
It's just a story, Bella.
Come on, let's go.
A snake! A snake!
♪ My mama said I didn't know
how to make a kitty meow ♪
Hello?
Gerald?
Hello.
Nice jacket.
Who are you?
It's always the same
inane questions.
"Who are you?"
"What do you want?"
"Why are you
doing this?"
James,
let's not play
with our food.
He's not here.
Whenever the weather's nice,
the Cullens disappear.
What, do they just ditch?
No, Dr. and Mrs. Cullen
yank them out for, like,
hiking and camping and stuff.
I tried that out
on my parents.
Not even close.
Guys, I'm going to
the prom with Eric.
I just asked him.
I took control.
I told you
that would happen.
Are you sure you
have to go out of town?
Oh, yeah,
it's a little
family thing.
Okay,
we should go shopping
in Port Angeles
before all
the good dresses
get cleaned out.
Port Angeles?
You mind if I come?
Yeah, I need your opinion.
I like this one.
That's cool.
But, like,
I don't know about
the one-shoulder thing.
I like this one.
Yeah,
I like the beading,
and you wouldn't
need jewelry.
Jess, what do you think?
Lavender?
Is that good?
Is that my color?
I like it.
I liked that
dusty rose one, too.
Okay, I like this one.
It makes my boobs
look good.
Hey.
Right?
Nice.
Oh, God.
That is uncomfortable.
That's disgusting.
Bella,
what do you think?
Yes?
That looks great.
You said that about,
like, the last five
dresses, though.
I thought they were
all pretty good.
You're not really
into this, are you?
I actually really
just want to go
to this bookstore.
I'll meet you guys
at the restaurant?
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah.
I'll see you in a minute.
Okay.
She's right, though.
This looks awesome.
There you go.
Have a good night.
Thank you.
Saw you
in the dress store.
Hey, where you running to?
There she is.
What's up?
It's my girl.
How you guys doing?
Look who we just found.
What's up, girl?
Hey... Where you going?
Where are you going?
Come get
a drink with us.
Yeah, you should
hang out with us.
Come on.
It's fun.
What's the problem?
She doesn't like that, man.
You're pretty.
Don't touch me.
Cute.
Really, no.
Seriously, you should.
Don't touch me.
Get in the car.
That was a very
dangerous maneuver.
I should go back there
and rip those guys'
heads off.
No, you shouldn't.
You don't know the vile,
repulsive things
they were thinking.
And you do?
It's not hard to guess.
Can you talk about
something else?
Distract me so
I won't turn around.
You should put
your seatbelt on.
I thought the salad
was pretty good.
Hey, you guys,
I'm sorry. I just...
Where were you?
We left you messages.
Yeah, we waited,
but we were, like,
starving, so we...
I'm sorry I kept
Bella from dinner.
We just sort of
ran into each other
and got talking.
Yeah.
No.
No, we totally understand.
I mean, that happens, right?
Yeah, we were...
We were, yeah,
we were just leaving. So...
Let's get this...
Bella, if you wanna...
I think I should make sure
Bella gets something to eat.
If you'd like.
I'll drive you home myself.
That's so thoughtful.
It's really thoughtful.
Yeah.
I should eat something.
Okay, so we'll
see you tomorrow.
Okay, yeah.
See ya.
Okay.
All right,
one mushroom ravioli.
Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
So are you sure
there isn't anything
I can get for you?
No. No, thank you.
Let me know.
You're really not gonna eat?
No, I'm on a special diet.
You gotta give me
some answers.
Yes, no.
To get to the other side.
1.77245...
I don't want to know
what the square root
of pi is.
You knew that?
How did you know where I was?
I didn't.
All right.
What?
Don't leave. I...
Did you follow me?
I feel very
protective of you.
So you followed me.
I was trying to keep
a distance unless
you needed my help,
and then I heard
what those low-lifes
were thinking.
Wait.
You say you heard
what they were thinking?
So what, you...
You read minds?
I can read every
mind in this room.
Apart from yours.
There's money, sex,
money,
sex,
cat.
And then you, nothing.
It's very frustrating.
Is there something
wrong with me?
See, I tell you
I can read minds,
and you think there's
something wrong with you.
What is it?
I don't have the strength
to stay away from you anymore.
Then don't.
Okay, I think
I'm warm enough now.
Your hand is so cold.
Whoa!
What is going on?
My dad's still here.
Can you pull in?
That's my father's
car on the end.
What is he doing here?
Carlisle,
what's going on?
Waylon Forge was
found in a boat
out near his place.
I just examined the body.
He died?
How?
Animal attack.
Was it the same one that
got that security guard
down in Mason?
Most likely.
Well, it's getting
closer to town, then.
Bella, you should go inside.
Waylon was your
father's friend.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Hey.
Dad, I'm really sorry.
I've known him
going on 30 years.
Don't worry,
we're gonna find
this thing.
Meantime,
I want you to
carry this with you.
I don't know if you...
It'll give your old man
some peace of mind.
Okay.
Let's go home.
Cold One.
You're impossibly
fast and strong.
Your skin is pale
white and ice-cold.
Your eyes change color.
And sometimes you speak like
you're from a different time.
You never eat
or drink anything.
You don't go out
in the sunlight.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
How long have you been 17?
A while.
I know what you are.
Say it.
Out loud.
Vampire.
Are you afraid?
No.
Then ask me
the most basic question.
What do we eat?
You won't hurt me.
Where are we going?
Up the mountain.
Out of the cloud bank.
You need to see
what I look like
in the sunlight.
This is why we don't show
ourselves in sunlight.
People would know
we're different.
This is what I am.
It's like diamonds.
You're beautiful.
Beautiful?
This is the skin
of a killer, Bella.
I'm a killer.
I don't believe that.
That's because
you believe the lie.
It's camouflage.
I'm the world's most
dangerous predator.
Everything about me
invites you in,
my voice, my face,
even my smell.
As if I would
need any of that.
As if you could outrun me!
As if you could
fight me off.
I'm designed to kill.
I don't care.
I've killed
people before.
It does not matter.
I wanted to kill you.
I've never wanted
a human's blood
so much in my life.
I trust you.
Don't.
I'm here. I trust you.
My family,
we're different from
others of our kind.
We only hunt animals.
We've learned to
control our thirst.
But it's you, your scent,
it's like a drug to me.
You're like my own
personal brand of heroin.
Why did you hate me
so much when we met?
I did.
Only for making me
want you so badly.
I still don't know
if I can control myself.
I know you can.
I can't read your mind.
You have to tell me
what you're thinking.
Now I'm afraid.
Good.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm only afraid
of losing you.
I feel like you're
gonna disappear.
You don't know how long
I've waited for you.
So the lion
fell in love
with the lamb.
What a stupid lamb.
What a sick,
masochistic lion.
About three things
I was absolutely positive.
First,
Edward was a vampire.
Second,
there was a part of him,
and I didn't know
how dominant
that part might be,
that thirsted for my blood.
And third,
I was unconditionally
and irrevocably
in love with him.
Monte Carlo?
That's our prom theme?
Gambling, tuxedos,
and Bond, James Bond.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
You know,
everybody's staring.
Not that guy.
No, he just looked.
I'm breaking all
the rules now anyway.
Since I'm going to hell.
So, does a person
have to be dying
to become like you?
No, that's just Carlisle.
He'd never do this
to someone who
had another choice.
So, how long have
you been like this?
Since 1918.
That's when Carlisle
found me dying
of Spanish influenza.
What was it like?
The venom was excruciating.
But what Carlisle did
was much harder.
Not many of us have
the restraint to do that.
But didn't he
just have to bite?
Not exactly.
When we taste
human blood,
a sort of frenzy begins,
and it's almost
impossible to stop.
But Carlisle did.
First with me
and then with his wife, Esme.
So is Carlisle
the real reason that
you don't kill people?
No, he's not
the only reason.
I don't want
to be a monster.
My family,
we think of ourselves
as vegetarians, right,
'cause we only survive
on the blood of animals.
But it's...
It's like a human
only living on tofu.
It keeps you strong,
but you're never
fully satisfied.
It wouldn't be like
drinking your blood,
for instance.
Was it other vampires
that killed Waylon?
Yeah.
There are others out there,
and we run into them
from time to time.
Can the rest of
your family read people's
minds like you can?
No. That's just me.
But Alice
can see the future.
I bet she saw me coming.
Alice's visions
are subjective.
I mean, the future
can always change.
Could you act human?
I mean,
I've got neighbors.
I'm gonna take you
to my place tomorrow.
Thanks.
Wait, like,
with your family?
Yeah.
What if they
don't like me?
So, you're worried
not because you'll be in
a house full of vampires,
but because you think
they won't approve of you?
I'm glad I amuse you.
What is it?
Complication.
I'll pick you
up tomorrow.
Hey. Come to visit your truck?
Looks good.
Got that dent out.
Yeah.
Actually, we came to
visit your flat-screen.
First Mariners game
of the season.
Plus Jacob here
keeps bugging me about
seeing you again.
Great, Dad. Thanks.
Just keeping it real, son.
Vitamin R.
Well done, Chief.
Harry Clearwater's
homemade fish fry.
Good man.
Any luck with
that Waylon case?
Well, I don't think
it was an animal
that killed him.
Never thought it was.
So spread the word
out at the rez, huh?
Keep the kids
out of the woods.
Will do.
Don't want no one else
getting hurt, do we?
Whoa.
This is incredible.
It's so light and open,
you know?
What did you expect,
coffins and dungeons
and moats?
No, not the moats.
Not the moats.
This is the one place
we don't have to hide.
I told them
not to do this.
You add
a little bit of olive oil
to a non-stick saute pan,
and you want to cook
with the olive oil
in medium-high heat.
What I do,
I cut this in strips,
and then we gonna cut this...
Is she even Italian?
Her name is Bella.
I'm sure she'll love it,
no matter what.
Get a whiff of that.
Here comes the human.
Bella, we're making
Italiano for you.
Bella, this is Esme.
My mother for all
intents and purposes.
You've given us an excuse
to use the kitchen
for the first time.
I hope you're hungry.
Yeah, absolutely.
She already ate.
Perfect.
Yeah, it's just because
I know that you guys
don't eat...
Of course. It's very
considerate of you.
Just ignore Rosalie. I do.
Yeah.
Let's just keep pretending
like this isn't dangerous
for all of us.
I would never tell
anybody anything.
She knows that.
Yeah, well,
the problem is, you two
have gone public now, so...
Emmett.
No, she should know.
The entire family
will be implicated
if this ends badly.
Badly, as in...
I would become the meal.
Hi, Bella.
I'm Alice.
Hi.
You do smell good.
Alice, what are you...
It's okay.
Bella and I are
gonna be great friends.
Sorry, Jasper's our
newest vegetarian.
It's a little
difficult for him.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's okay, Jasper.
You won't hurt her.
All right, I'm gonna
take you on a tour of
the rest of the house.
Okay.
Well, I'll see you soon.
Cute!
I know.
I think that went well.
Clean this up. Now.
Was that as weird for
you as it was for me?
I don't know.
Graduation caps?
Yeah. It's a private joke.
We matriculate a lot.
That's kind of miserable.
I mean,
repeating high school
over and over.
True, but the younger
we start out in a new place,
the longer we can stay there.
Come on.
Yeah, this is my room.
No bed?
No, I don't...
I don't sleep.
Ever?
No, not at all.
Okay.
Boy, you have so much music.
What are you listening to?
It's Debussy.
I don't know...
Yeah.
Claire De Lune  is great.
What?
I can't dance.
Well, I could
always make you.
I'm not scared of you.
Well, you really
shouldn't have said that.
You better hold on tight,
spider monkey.
Do you trust me?
In theory.
Then close your eyes.
What?
This isn't real.
This kind of stuff
just doesn't exist.
It does in my world.
Hold up.
It's human.
Arizona.
Yo, what's happening?
So you and Cullen, huh?
That's...
I don't like it.
I mean, I don't know,
he just looks at you
like you're something
to eat.
Here's your veggie
plate, Stephenie.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Biology project.
I ordered you
the spinach salad.
I hope that's okay.
You should order one
for yourself next time.
Cut back on the steak.
Hey, I'm as healthy
as a horse.
Say, Chief,
boys want to know,
did you find anything
down by Queets River today?
Yeah, we found
a bare human footprint,
but it looks like
whoever that is,
is headed east,
so Kitsap County sheriff
is gonna take over from here.
Okay.
Okay?
I just hope
they catch him fast.
Looks like your friends
are flagging you.
It's okay if you
wanna go join them.
I'm just gonna
turn in early anyway.
Me, too.
Bella, it's Friday night.
Go out.
Looks like the Newton boy's
got a big smile for you.
Yeah, he's a good buddy.
What about any of these
other yahoos in town?
Anybody interest you?
Dad, we gonna
talk about boys?
Yeah, I guess not.
I just feel like
I leave you alone
too much.
You should be around people.
I don't really
mind being alone.
I guess I'm kind of
like my dad in that way.
So, how's all
the baseball stuff going?
Phil's working so hard.
You know,
spring training.
We're looking for a house
to rent in case things
become more permanent.
You'd like Jacksonville,
baby.
Yeah?
I'm really liking Forks.
What?
Forks is growing on me.
Could a guy
have anything
to do with that?
Well, yeah.
I knew it.
Tell me everything.
What is he? Jock? Indie?
I bet he's smart.
Is he smart?
Mom, can I talk to you later?
Come on,
we gotta talk boys.
Are you being safe?
How did you get in here?
The window.
Do you do that a lot?
Well, just the past
couple of months.
I like watching you sleep.
It's kind of
fascinating to me.
I always want
to try one thing.
Just stay very still.
Don't move.
Stop it!
I'm sorry.
I'm stronger
than I thought.
Yeah. I wish
I could say the same.
I can't ever lose
control with you.
Hey, don't go.
Hey, got you another one.
Thanks.
I have a date
with Edward Cullen.
He's a little old
for you, isn't he?
No.
He's a junior.
I'm a junior.
I thought you
liked the Cullens.
I thought you didn't like
any of the boys in town.
Edward doesn't live in town.
Technically.
He's right outside.
He is?
Yeah, he wanted to
meet you, officially.
All right. Bring him in.
Could you be nice?
He's important.
Chief Swan.
I want to formally
introduce myself.
I'm Edward Cullen.
Hi, Edward.
Bella won't be out
too late tonight.
She's just gonna play
baseball with my family.
Baseball?
Yes, sir,
that's the plan.
Bella's gonna play baseball.
Well, good luck with that.
I'll take
good care of her.
I promise.
Hey.
Still got that
pepper spray?
Yeah, Dad.
And since when do
vampires like baseball?
Well,
it's the American pastime,
and there's
a thunderstorm coming.
It's the only time
we can play.
You'll see why.
Hey.
Glad you're here.
We need an umpire.
She thinks we cheat.
I know you cheat.
Call them as you
see them, Bella.
Okay.
It's time.
Okay, now I see why
you need the thunder.
That's gotta be
a home run, right?
Edward's very fast.
♪ Ooh, baby,
don't you know I suffer?
I'm a fool for you
Come home, Rosalie!
You're out.
Out!
Babe, come on.
It's just a game.
♪ You set my soul alight
Nice kitty.
♪ Ooh
♪ You set my soul alight
What are you doing?
♪ Super massive black hole
♪ Super massive black hole ♪
My monkey man.
Stop!
They were leaving.
Then they heard us.
Let's go.
It's too late.
Get your hair down.
Like that'll help.
I can smell her
from across the field.
I shouldn't have
brought you here.
I'm so sorry.
What? What are you...
Just be quiet
and stand behind me.
I believe this
belongs to you.
Thank you.
I am Laurent.
And this is Victoria
and James.
I'm Carlisle.
This is my family.
Hello.
I'm afraid your
hunting activities
have caused something
of a mess for us.
Our apologies.
We didn't realize
the territory
had been claimed.
Yes, well,
we maintain a permanent
residence nearby.
Really?
Well, we won't be
a problem anymore.
We were just passing through.
The humans were tracking us,
but we led them east.
You should be safe.
Excellent.
So,
could you use
three more players?
Come on. Just one game.
Sure. Why not?
A few of us were leaving.
You could take their place.
We'll bat first.
I'm the one with
the wicked curveball.
Well, I think
we can handle that.
We shall see.
You brought a snack.
A human?
The girl is with us.
I think it best
if you leave.
I can see the game is over.
We'll go now.
James.
Get Bella out of here.
Go.
Okay, I've got it!
I've got it!
I'm all right!
What,
now he's coming
after me?
Listen to me.
James is a tracker.
The hunt is his obsession.
I read his mind.
My reaction on
the field set him off.
I just made this
his most exciting
game ever.
He's never gonna stop.
What should we do?
We have to kill him.
Rip him apart
and burn the pieces.
Where we going?
Away from Forks.
We'll get a ferry
to Vancouver.
I have to go home. Now.
You have to take me home.
You can't go home.
He's just gonna
trace your scent there.
It's the first place
he's gonna look.
But my dad is there. We...
It doesn't matter!
Yes, it does!
He could get killed
because of us!
Just let me get you
out of here first,
all right?
It's my dad!
We have to go back!
We'll figure a way
to lead the tracker
away somehow.
I don't know.
But we have to
do something.
Edward,
I said leave me alone.
Bella, don't do this, please.
It's over! Get out!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Bella? What's going on?
I just gotta
get out of here.
I'm leaving now.
Hey.
Bella?
What am I gonna
say to him?
I can't hurt him.
Bella, what's going on?
You just have to.
I'll be down
at the truck.
Did he hurt you?
No.
Break up with you
or something?
No, I broke up
with him.
I thought you liked him.
Yeah, that's why
I have to leave.
I don't want this.
I have to go home.
Home? Your...
Your mom's
not even in Phoenix.
She'll come home.
I'll call her from the road.
You're not gonna
drive home right now.
You can sleep on it.
If you still feel like
going in the morning,
I'll take you to the airport.
No. I want to drive.
It'll give me
more time to think.
I mean,
if I get really tired,
I'll pull into a motel.
I promise.
Look, Bella,
I know I'm not that
much fun to be around,
but I can change that.
We can do more
stuff together.
Like what?
Like watch baseball
on the flat-screen?
Eat at the diner
every night?
Steak and cobbler?
Dad, that's you.
That's not me.
Bella, come on,
I just...
I just got you back.
Yeah, and, you know,
if I don't get out now,
then I'm just gonna be
stuck here like Mom.
Your father's
gonna forgive you.
Why don't you let me drive?
He won't.
You should've seen his face.
I told him the same thing
that my mom told him
when she was leaving him.
It's the only way
he'd let you go.
Just don't worry
about him now.
He's safe.
The tracker's following us.
Oh, God.
It's just Emmett.
Alice is in
the car behind us.
Wait.
He came to warn
us about James.
This isn't my fight,
and I've grown tired
of his games,
but he's got
unparalleled senses,
absolutely lethal.
I've never seen
anything like him
in my 300 years.
And the woman, Victoria,
don't underestimate her.
I've had to fight
our kind before.
We're not easy to kill.
But not impossible.
We'll tear them apart
and burn the pieces.
I don't relish the thought
of killing another creature,
even a sadistic
one like James.
What if he kills
one of us first?
I'm gonna run
Bella south.
Can you lead the tracker
away from here?
No, Edward.
James knows you would
never leave Bella.
He'll follow you.
I'll go with Bella.
Jasper and I
will drive her south.
I'll keep her safe, Edward.
Can you keep your
thoughts to yourself?
Yes.
Rosalie, Esme,
could you put these on
so the tracker will
pick up Bella's scent?
Why? What is she to me?
Rosalie,
Bella is with Edward.
She's part of
this family now,
and we protect our family.
Oh, God. If anything...
What if...
If anything happens,
I swear to God...
Nothing's gonna happen.
There's seven of us,
and there's two of them,
and when everything's done,
I'm gonna come back
and get you.
Yeah.
Bella,
you are my life now.
Hey, Mom. It's me again.
You must have
let your phone die
or something.
I'm not in Forks,
but everything's okay,
and I'll explain it later.
Rosalie, mark the tree.
That's good.
What is it?
What do you see?
He's figured it out.
The tracker,
he just changed course.
Where will it
take him, Alice?
Mirrors.
A room full of mirrors.
Edward said the visions
weren't always certain.
She sees the course people
are on while they're on it.
If they change their minds,
the vision changes.
Okay, so the course that
the tracker's on now
is gonna lead him
to a ballet studio?
You've been here?
I took lessons as a kid.
The school I went to
had an arch just like that.
Was your school
here in Phoenix?
Yeah.
Edward, are you okay?
We've lost the tracker.
The woman's
still in the area.
Rosalie and Esme
are going back to Forks
to protect your father.
I'm coming to get you.
Then you and I
are gonna go somewhere alone.
And the others
will keep hunting.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make you safe again.
Hey, Mom,
I'm glad you got my message.
What are you doing home?
Bella? Bella?
Bella, where are you?
Calm down,
everything's fine.
Bella? Bella?
I'll explain
everything later.
Mom, are you there?
Forks High School
doesn't protect its students'
privacy very well.
It was just too easy
for Victoria to find
your previous address.
It's a nice house
you have here.
I was prepared
to wait for you,
but then Mom came home
after she received a very
worried call from your dad,
and it all worked
out quite well.
Wait, wait...
Don't touch her! Don't...
You can still save her.
Don't!
But you're gonna
have to get away
from your friends.
Can you handle that?
Where should I meet you?
How about your
old ballet studio?
And I'll know if you
bring anyone along.
Poor Mommy would
pay the price
for that mistake.
I'd never given much thought
to how I would die.
But dying in the place
of someone I love
seems like a good way to go.
I can't bring myself
to regret the decisions
that brought me
face-to-face with death.
They also
brought me to Edward.
Bella? Bella?
Bella, where are you?
Mom?
Bella?
There you are.
What are you
doing in here?
Everyone makes fun of me.
Come on,
you're a wonderful dancer.
Mom, I suck.
You do not suck.
That's my favorite part.
You were a stubborn child,
weren't you?
She's not even here.
No.
Sorry.
You know, but you really
made it too easy.
So to make things
more entertaining,
I'm gonna make
a little film of
our time together.
I borrowed this
from your house.
I hope you don't mind.
Good.
And
action.
That'll break
Edward's little heart.
You have...
Edward has nothing
to do with this!
But he does.
His rage will make for
more interesting sport
than his feeble attempt
to protect you.
And let's continue.
Beautiful.
Very visually dynamic.
I chose my stage well.
It's too bad he didn't have
the strength to turn you.
Instead, he kept you
this fragile little human.
It's cruel, really.
Tell Edward
how much it hurts.
Tell him to avenge you.
Tell him!
No, Edward, don't!
Tell him! Tell him!
You're alone
'cause you're faster
than the others.
But not stronger.
I'm strong enough to kill you.
I'm sorry.
Bella, Bella, it's okay.
Son. Enough.
Remember who you are.
Bella, you're okay.
Bella needs you.
It's okay.
Oh, God.
Carlisle? Her blood.
Your brothers will
take care of him.
I got him.
Carlisle!
Start the fire.
Get the floorboards.
Alice!
Alice, go.
Her femoral artery's
been severed.
She's losing too much blood.
No, no, my head is burning!
It's the venom.
You have to make a choice.
You could let
the change happen.
No.
It's gonna happen, Edward.
I've seen it.
It doesn't have
to be that way.
She's still hemorrhaging.
Alice,
make me a tourniquet.
Your belt.
Carlisle,
what's my other option?
Tie it above my hands.
Carlisle!
Go.
We could try to
suck the venom out.
You know I won't
be able to stop.
Then find the will to stop.
But choose.
She only has minutes left.
I'm gonna make
it go away, Bella.
I'm gonna make it go away.
Edward, stop.
Her blood is clean.
You're killing her.
Edward.
Stop.
Find the will.
Death is peaceful, easy.
Life is harder.
Bella?
Baby?
Bella.
Mom?
Hey.
Where is he?
Where's...
Where's Edward?
He's asleep.
He never leaves.
And your dad,
he's down at the cafeteria.
What happened?
Well, when you fell,
you broke your leg,
and you lost a lot of blood.
You don't remember
any of this, do you?
Edward came down with his dad
to try to convince you
to come back to Forks.
So you went over
to their hotel,
then you tripped,
and you fell down
two flights of stairs.
Went through a window.
Yeah, that sounds like me.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
It's Phil.
He's so worried about you.
You're texting.
Finally, yeah.
I told him to
stay down in Florida.
Honey, you are gonna
love Jacksonville.
It's sunny every day,
and we found
the cutest little house,
and you've got
your own bathroom.
Mom, I still want
to live in Forks.
What?
I want to live in Forks.
Well, okay,
but we'll talk about it.
Do you mind getting Dad?
I have to talk to him.
Apologize.
Okay, baby.
I'll go get him.
And I'll go
get a nurse, okay?
Okay.
So what happened?
Where's James?
We took care of it.
And the woman,
Victoria, she ran off.
I'm alive because of you.
No, you're in here
because of me.
The worst part of it was that
I thought I wasn't
gonna be able to stop.
You did stop.
Bella,
you gotta go to Jacksonville
so I can't hurt you anymore.
What?
Are you... No!
No!
I don't even know
what you're... How...
What are you talking about?
You want me to go away?
I can't...
No, I can't...
I can't just leave you...
I know.
We can't be apart.
You can't leave me.
I'm here.
Okay, just don't...
You just can't say
stuff like that to me. Ever.
Where else am I gonna go?
Alice lent me the dress.
The cast is...
You're perfect.
I'll take care of her,
Chief Swan.
Uh-huh.
I've heard that before.
All right, Bells.
I put a new can of
pepper spray in your bag.
Dad.
And...
Well, you look beautiful.
Thanks.
See you.
Hey. I'll be right back.
Bella.
Jacob.
Hey.
Nice.
You, too.
Are you crashing
the prom or something?
Did you come with a date?
No.
My dad paid me
to come talk to you.
Twenty bucks.
Let's hear it.
Just don't get mad, okay?
He wants you to break up
with your boyfriend.
It's just, he said, quote,
"We'll be watching you."
Okay, well,
tell him, "Thanks."
Okay.
And to pay up.
Okay. Let me help you.
Jacob.
I'll take it from here.
Guess I'll see
you around, Bella.
All right.
I leave you alone
for two minutes,
and the wolves descend.
I can't believe
you're making me do this.
Just smile.
♪ Tonight! Lightning Strikes!
♪ Let's go into Twilight!
Wow. You are really
trying to kill me.
The prom is an important
rite of passage.
I didn't want you
to miss anything.
Oh.
♪ Everyday
we're going all the way
♪ Everyday, everyday, everyday
♪ Tonight!
Lightning Strikes! ♪
Bella, hey!
Do you want to go?
Yeah.
All right,
slowing it down.
Shall we?
You're serious?
Why not.
♪ Wide on my plastic toys
♪ Then when the cops
closed the fair
♪ I cut my long baby hair
♪ Stole me a dog-eared map
See, you're dancing.
At prom.
♪ Have I found you
♪ Flightless bird
♪ Jealous
♪ Weeping
Edward, why did you save me?
If you just let
the venom spread,
I could be
like you by now.
You don't know
what you're saying.
You don't want this.
I want you.
Always.
I'm not gonna end
your life for you.
I'm dying already.
Every second, I get closer.
Older.
That's the way
it's supposed to be.
Alice said that
she saw me like you.
I heard her.
Her visions change.
Yeah, based on
what people decide.
I've decided.
So that's what
you dream about.
Becoming a monster.
I dream about
being with you forever.
Forever?
And you're ready
right now?
Yes.
♪ Bleeding or lost you
♪ American mouth
♪ Big pill
Is it not enough
just to have a long
and happy life with me?
Yeah.
For now.
No one will
surrender tonight,
but I won't give in.
I know what I want.
♪ Have I found you
♪ Flightless bird
♪ Grounded
♪ Bleeding or lost you
♪ American mouth ♪
♪ How come I end up
where I started
where I went wrong
♪ Won't take my eyes
off the ball again
♪ You reel me out
when you cut the string
♪ How come I end up
where I started
where I went wrong
♪ Won't take my eyes
off the ball again
♪ First you reel me out
and then you cut the string
♪ You used to be alright
♪ What happened?
♪ Did the cat get your tongue
♪ Did your string come undone
♪ One by one
♪ It comes to us all
♪ It's as soft
as your pillow ♪
♪ I dreamed I was missing
♪ You were so scared
♪ But no one would listen
♪ 'Cause no one else cared
♪ After my dreaming
♪ I woke with this fear
♪ What am I leaving
♪ When I'm done here?
♪ So if you're asking me
♪ I want you to know
♪ When my time comes
♪ Forget the wrong
that I've done
♪ Help me leave behind some
♪ Reasons to be missed
♪ Don't resent me
♪ And when
you're feeling empty
♪ Keep me in your memory
♪ Leave out all the rest
♪ Forgetting
all the hurt inside
♪ You've learned
to hide so well
♪ Pretending
someone else can come
♪ And save me from myself
♪ I can't be who you are
♪ When my time comes
♪ Forget the wrong
that I've done
♪ Help me leave behind some
♪ Reasons to be missed
♪ Don't resent me
♪ And when
you're feeling empty
♪ Keep me in your memory
♪ Leave out all the rest
♪ Forgetting
all the hurt inside
♪ You've learned
to hide so well
♪ Pretending
someone else can come
♪ And save me from myself
♪ I can't be who you are
♪ I can't be who you are ♪
♪ How can I decide
what's right
♪ When you're
clouding up my mind
♪ I can't win
your losing fight
♪ All the time
♪ How can I ever
own what's mine
♪ When you're always
taking sides
♪ But you won't
take away my pride
♪ No, not this time
♪ How did we get here?
♪ When I used to
know you so well
♪ But how did we get here?
♪ I think I know
♪ The truth is
hiding in your eyes
♪ And its hanging
on your tongue
♪ Just boiling in my blood
♪ But you think
that I can't see
♪ What kind of man
that you are
♪ If you're a man at all
♪ Well, I will figure
this one out on my own
♪ I'm screaming I love you so
♪ My thoughts you can't decode
♪ How did we get here?
♪ When I used to
know you so well
♪ Yeah
But how did we get here?
♪ Well, I think I know how
♪ Do you see what we've done
♪ We're gonna make
such fools of ourselves
♪ How did we get here?
♪ When I used to
know you so well
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
♪ How did we get here?
♪ When I used to
know you so well
♪ I think I know
♪ There is something
I see in you
♪ It might kill me