ARO: Ah!
Valentina has
brought us something.
She should not have interrupted.
She's new.
Aren't they all?
Ah!
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Edward and Bella
are to be married.
What joy!
This is the Cullens' way of
announcing her transformation.
They mock us with their delays.
Patience, brother.
Though you do have a point.
The human did interrupt.
Oh, I do love weddings.
No!
BELLA: "Childhood is not
from birth to a certain age.
"And at a certain age, the child is
grown and puts away childish things.
"Childhood is the kingdom
where nobody dies."
Jake! Jacob!
(ROARING)
Phil!
It's happening.
(SCRAPING)
You just have to break them in.
I've been breaking them in.
For three days.
Can I just go barefoot?
No, absolutely not.
Just thinking it's
a little much, you know?
The dress and the shoes,
and all of this.
ALICE:
No, it's exactly enough.
Tomorrow will be perfect.
Where do you want them, boss?
On either side of the aisle.
What aisle?
Does no one have vision?
You, go home and get
lots of beauty sleep.
That's an order.
Okay.
I was just checking
for cold feet.
Well, mine are toasty warm.
It's not too late
to change your mind.
What? Now you're
having second thoughts?
You are.
No, I've been waiting a
century to marry you, Miss Swan.
But?
I haven't told you
everything about myself.
What? You're not a virgin?
(LAUGHS)
(EXHALING)
Look, you can't
scare me away now.
Look, a few years
after Carlisle created me,
I rebelled against him.
I resented him for
curbing my appetite.
And so for a while,
I went off on my own.
I wanted to know
how it felt to hunt.
(SCREAMING)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS)
EDWARD: To taste human blood.
(HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
(CHOKING)
All the men I killed
were monsters.
And so was I.
Edward, they were all murderers.
You probably saved
more lives than you took.
Bella, that's what
I told myself.
But they were all human beings.
I looked into their eyes as
they died and I saw who I was,
and what I was capable of.
And what I'll be capable of.
Why are you
telling me this tonight?
Did you really think this was
gonna change my mind about you?
I just wondered if it would
change your mind about yourself,
and who you wanna see when you
look in the mirror a year from now.
I know I can do this.
Let me tell you why.
Because you did.
(SCOFFS)
You should give yourself
some credit for that.
Now, hopefully, a year from now,
I'm gonna look in the mirror
and see someone like you.
I mean, someone capable of
courage and sacrifice and love.
(EMMETT WHISTLES)
What is that?
EMMETT: Come on! Let's go!
I'm late for my bachelor party.
Send him out, Bella,
or we're coming in after him.
So, this party.
Will there be strippers?
(LAUGHS)
No, just a couple of mountain
lions. Maybe a few bears.
Don't worry, Bella, we'll give
him back in plenty of time.
Okay, go, before
they break my house.
EMMETT: Let's go! Let's go!
I'll meet you at the altar.
I'll be the one in white.
That was very convincing.
(ALL LAUGHING)
What did I say
about beauty sleep?
Sorry, bad dream.
It was wedding jitters.
Do you need some help?
I could do her hair.
Really?
Please. I'm not offended
by your choice of groom.
Just my blatant lack of
respect for mortality.
Essentially.
Weddings. They bring
everyone together.
Hey, so, did you find
our daughter?
Are those graduation caps?
(LAUGHS) How creative!
Or weird.
Alice? Bella?
BELLA: In here, Mom.
(GASPS) Oh, my gosh!
You're so beautiful.
Oh, honey.
Crap! My mascara.
Mom!
Thanks.
Charlie, get in here.
You sure? I don't wanna...
I know. I look hot.
(LAUGHING)
We thought you
needed something blue.
And something old.
Besides your mother.
(SCOFFS) Nice.
It was Grandma Swan's.
But we added the sapphires.
It's beautiful, you guys.
Wow. Thank you so much.
It's your first family heirloom.
Pass on to your daughter,
and her daughter.
Mom, I love it.
Nope. No smudging
my masterpiece.
She's right.
Thank you.
ALICE: Okay.
Time for the dress!
(GASPS)
ALICE: Do you wanna see it?
RENEE: I want to see it!
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
ERIC: They have
got to be related.
What a gene pool.
ERIC: Seriously.
You've got some...
The drool.
So, you think
Bella's gonna be showing?
Jess, she is not pregnant.
Okay. Who else
gets married at 18?
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(SIGHING)
You ready?
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
Just don't let me fall, Dad.
Never.
MINISTER: Ladies and gentlemen,
we are gathered here on this glorious day
to witness the union of
Edward Cullen and Bella Swan.
Please repeat after me.
I, Edward Cullen.
- MINISTER: Take you, Bella Swan.
- EDWARD: Take you, Bella Swan.
MINISTER: To have and to hold.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
To have and to hold.
For better or for worse.
For richer, for poorer.
In sickness and in health.
To love.
To cherish.
As long as we both shall live.
I do.
I love you.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(PLAYING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
Just thought it'd be bigger.
Yeah.
Hi!
Hi, guys.
We were just saying how pretty
everything is, you know, just saying.
Well, thanks so much.
You don't think it's too much?
No.
Not at all.
Hey, man. Nice to see you.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
I hope you'll be happy, Bella.
Thank you, Billy.
Have you heard from him?
I'm sure Jake
wishes you the best.
Well, I plan on getting drunk.
They're serving up
some pretty fancy champagne.
Sue, can I get you a glass?
Sparkling fire water.
Sounds great.
CARMEN: Bella.
Congratulations, Edward.
Thank you.
Bella.
Eleazar and Carmen, right?
Mmm-hmm.
Hola.
Yes, and these are
our cousins from Alaska.
Tanya, Kate. We've
heard so much about you.
Welcome to the family.
Bienvenida.
BELLA: Thank you.
Irina.
Come meet Bella.
I can't do this.
You promised.
They invited one.
Irina, he's our friend.
They killed Laurent.
He tried to kill Bella.
I don't believe that.
He wanted to be like us.
To live in peace with humans.
With me.
I'm sorry.
CARMEN: Irina!
ELEAZAR: Well.
Let's not monopolize
the bride. Congratulations.
BELLA: Thank you.
Sorry.
Well, what's a wedding
without some family drama?
Yeah.
EMMETT: Excuse me.
Is this on?
Hello?
(MAN WOLF-WHISTLES)
Umm...
I'd like to propose a toast.
To my new sister.
Bella, I hope you've gotten
enough sleep these last 18 years.
'Cause you won't be getting
any more for a while (CHUCKLES)
(SILENCE)
Well, Bella was just like everybody
else, totally mesmerized by Edward.
Or "The Hair," as I call him.
And then, suddenly,
Edward is all about Bella.
Even though she's not the
captain of the volleyball team.
I'm just kidding.
Or the president of
the student council.
Edward will be a good husband.
I know this because I'm a cop.
I know things.
Like how to hunt somebody
to the ends of the Earth.
(GUESTS LAUGHING)
Now that you're my sister,
you'll have to get over
your aversion to fashion.
And I know how to use a gun.
Skirts, heels, handbags.
(SINGING LULLABY)
I'd like to thank
Renee and Charlie
for bringing such a wonderful
person into the world and into our lives.
We will cherish and
protect her forever.
It's an extraordinary thing
to meet someone
who you can bare your soul to.
And who will accept
you for what you are.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
I've been waiting, what
seems like a very long time,
to get beyond what I am.
And with Bella,
I feel like I can finally begin.
So I'd like to propose a toast
to my beautiful bride.
No measure of time with you
will be long enough.
But let's start with forever.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoa!
Another one of your
gifts just arrived.
What?
Yeah, come on.
What's a wedding
present doing out here?
Just a little more private.
The best man didn't
have time to get a tux.
Jacob!
Jacob.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey.
Hey, Bella.
This is kind of you.
Kind is my middle name.
I'll see if
Rosalie wants to dance.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Doesn't matter.
Everything's perfect now.
Will you dance with me?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Where have you been?
We were gonna put your face
on a milk carton.
Mostly northern Canada.
I think.
It's weird to be back on
two legs again, in clothes.
Gotten out of practice
with the whole human thing.
Are you okay?
Being here?
Why? Afraid I'll trash
your party?
(SOFT GROWLING)
You're not the only one.
You'd think I'd be used to
telling you goodbye by now.
Come on, you're not supposed
to be the one crying, Bella.
Everyone cries at weddings.
This is how I'm
gonna remember you.
Pink cheeks.
Two left feet.
Heartbeat.
'Cause what, soon I'm
gonna be dead to you?
No.
I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to appreciate
your last night as a human.
Well, it's not my last night.
I thought you...
I didn't really wanna spend
my honeymoon writhing in pain.
What's the point?
It's not like you're gonna have a
real honeymoon with him, anyway.
It's gonna be as
real as anyone else's.
That's a sick joke.
You are joking?
What? While you're
still human?
You can't be serious, Bella.
Tell me you're not that stupid.
I mean, it's really
none of your business.
No! You can't do this!
Jake.
Listen to me, Bella.
Jake, let me go!
Jacob, calm down, all right?
Are you out of your mind? Huh?
You'll kill her!
Walk away, Jake.
Enough, Jacob!
Stay out of this, Sam.
You're not gonna start
something that we'll have to finish.
She'll die.
She's not our concern anymore.
Let's go, Seth!
BELLA: I'm really,
really, really stupid.
No, it's all right.
Come on, people are probably
missing us. Let's go back.
(ALL CHEERING)
So, he really won't tell you
where he's taking you?
No, it's a surprise.
(LAUGHS)
Well, wear a hat.
Sunscreen.
Take care of yourself.
I will.
Okay.
I love you, Bella.
I love you.
So much.
Thank you.
Everything's
packed and ready to go.
Cool.
Oh.
I'm gonna go see him.
Yeah.
Dad.
(CHUCKLES QUIETLY)
Well...
It's gonna be strange,
you not living under my roof.
Yeah.
It's gonna be
strange for me, too.
You know it will
always be your home, right?
I love you, Dad. Forever.
I love you, too, Bells.
I always have and I always will.
All right.
Go on.
You don't wanna miss your plane.
Wherever it's going.
(LAUGHS)
Okay.
Bye.
You ready?
(GUESTS CHEERING)
Yeah, I'm ready.
(WOLF HOWLING)
(SAMBA MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE SINGING IN PORTUGUESE)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
So, we're not staying in Rio?
No, we're just passing through.
Are we close?
EDWARD: That's Isle Esme.
It was a gift from Carlisle.
(SQUEALS)
Is this totally necessary?
I am nothing if not traditional.
You wanna take a look around?
You tired?
(SIGHING)
Do you wanna go for a swim?
Yeah, that sounds nice.
I could use a few human minutes.
Don't take too long,
Mrs. Cullen.
(SIGHING) Okay.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXHALING)
Okay.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Alice!
(EXHALING)
Don't be a coward. (SCOFFS)
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
You're so beautiful.
I promised that we'd try.
If this doesn't work...
I trust you.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GIGGLING)
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
It's okay.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
EDWARD:
How badly are you hurt?
What?
No, Bella, look.
Bella, I can't tell
you how sorry I am.
I'm not.
Really, I'm not.
I'm fine.
Don't say you're fine.
Just don't.
No, you don't.
Don't ruin this.
I've already ruined it.
Why can't you see how
perfectly happy I am?
Or was five seconds ago.
I mean, now I'm sort
of pissed off, actually.
You should be angry with me.
I mean, we knew this was
gonna be tricky, right?
I think we did amazing.
I mean, it was amazing for me.
That's what
you're worried about?
That I didn't enjoy myself?
I know it's not
the same for you,
but for a human, I can't imagine
that it gets any
better than that.
Last night
was the best
night of my existence.
You're the best.
You're not gonna
touch me again, are you?
You know that's not what I mean.
Let me make you breakfast.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHS)
(EDWARD FAKES SNORING)
(WHOOPS)
I win.
(LAUGHTER ECHOING)
Bella?
You having a nightmare?
No.
(SNIFFLING)
It was just a dream.
It was a really good dream.
Then why are you crying?
Because I wanted it to be real.
Tell me.
Bella, I can't.
Please.
JACOB: Maybe they'll say
she was in a car crash.
Or tripped and fell off a cliff.
PAUL: Keep it in play!
Keep it in play!
Come on!
(PLAYERS LAUGHING)
Come on! Come on!
At least I'll get
one thing out of it.
No, you won't.
Cullens are not a danger
to the town or the tribe.
Well, he's either gonna
kill her or change her.
And the treaty says...
I say, Jacob.
I say.
You know, if you wanted things
different, you should've become alpha.
Turning it down seemed
like a good idea at the time.
Jake, you really think you could kill
Bella if she comes back a vampire?
No, make one of us do it,
then hold a grudge against us.
Shut up, Leah.
Would you just get over it? It's
not like you've imprinted on her.
At least they seem happy.
Yeah, some people are
just lucky, I guess.
Lucky?
None of them belong
to themselves anymore.
And the sickest part is their genes
tell them they're happy about it.
Least if you
imprinted on someone,
you'd finally
forget about Bella.
I mean, being any kind of happy
is better than being miserable
about someone you can't have.
Pillows survived.
Practice makes perfect, right?
I told you that.
That smells amazing.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm starving.
You realize how many eggs you've
gone through since you've been here?
This island must have messed
with my appetite or something.
I'm gonna get fat here.
(LAUGHS)
Eat as many eggs as you like. Pretty
soon you won't want them anymore.
Or cheeseburgers. Or
chocolate. Or ice cream.
Well, maybe
it doesn't have to be
so soon.
Will you wait?
Look, I can't
understand you at all.
Look, I did not know
how good being human could be.
(SIGHS)
So sex was the key after all.
If I'd have known that,
I could have saved
myself a lot of arguments.
Yeah, you probably could have.
Just hold that thought.
(CHATTING QUIETLY)
Bella, these are our
housekeepers, Gustavo and Kaure.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Well, I guess we
just leave them to it.
What was that all about?
She's afraid for you.
Why?
Because I have
you here all alone.
You mean she knows about you?
She suspects.
She's native Ticuna. They have
legends about blood-drinking demons
who prey on beautiful women.
(EXCLAIMING IN PORTUGUESE)
Hey.
(LAUGHS)
You're late.
(RETCHING)
Bella?
Hey, don't come in here.
You don't need to see this.
"In sickness and health,"
remember?
It must have been the chicken.
Could you grab my bag?
What is it?
How many days has it been
since the wedding?
Fourteen. Why?
Will you tell me
what's going on?
I'm late.
My period, it's late.
That's impossible.
Can this happen?
Whoa!
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Alice.
ALICE: Bella?
Are you all right?
I'm not 100% sure.
Why? What's wrong? I just...
You just what?
Alice, what did you see?
Here's Carlisle.
CARLISLE:
Bella, what's going on?
I don't know. I'm a little worried.
Can vampires go into shock?
Has Edward been harmed?
No.
I know that it's impossible,
but I think that I'm pregnant.
Whoa!
Carlisle, I swear, something
just moved inside me.
Is this even possible?
I don't know.
What's he saying?
The sooner Bella's here, the
sooner we can find out what it is.
I need you to get to
the mainland at once.
Yeah, yeah, I will.
Well?
Damn it.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Kaure's making sure
you're still alive.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(EDWARD AND KAURE ARGUING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
What?
Her people have legends.
She might have seen this before.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
I'm not gonna let it hurt you.
Carlisle will
get that thing out.
Thing?
Wait here while we load.
ROSALIE: Hello?
Rosalie.
Bella?
What's going on?
I need your help.
Hey, Son.
What's going on?
Bella called him.
Hey, haven't seen you
in a while.
You okay?
So, you finally
heard from Bella?
They're extending their trip.
Seems she caught a bug.
They wanna wait until she
feels better before they travel.
She's sick.
Yeah, she told me not to
worry, but she sounded,
I don't know, off.
She'll be okay, Charlie.
Come on. Let's eat.
Jacob, let it go.
Is it true?
Hello, Jacob, how are you?
Listen, just
give it to me straight.
BELLA: Jake, is that you?
She's here? They came
home two weeks ago.
Jake.
BELLA: I'm glad you came.
Close enough.
What's your problem?
BELLA: Rose, it's okay.
(SIGHS)
You look terrible.
Yeah, it's nice to see you, too.
So, are you gonna tell me
what's wrong with you?
Rose, you wanna help me up?
You did this!
We didn't know it
was even possible.
What is it?
CARLISLE: I'm not sure.
Ultrasounds and needles won't
penetrate the embryonic sac.
I can't see it, either.
And I can't see
Bella's future anymore.
CARLISLE: We've been researching
legends, but there isn't much to go on.
What we do know is
that it's strong.
And fast-growing.
Why haven't you done
anything? Take it out of her!
This is none of
your business, dog.
Rose!
All this fighting
isn't good for Bella.
The fetus isn't good for Bella.
Say the word, Alice. "Baby."
It's just a little baby.
Carlisle, you've gotta
do something.
No.
It's not his decision.
It's not any of yours.
Jacob, I need to talk to you.
I always knew you'd destroy her.
She thinks Carlisle can
turn her at the last minute,
like he did for me and Esme.
Can he?
Probability is slight.
And if her heart fails...
Look, Jacob, I need you
to do something for me.
(SCOFFS)
For her.
You have a connection with her
that I'll never understand.
Maybe you could talk to her,
change her mind.
You can keep her alive.
And if I can't?
If she dies,
you get what you always wanted.
To kill me.
Rose, I'm fine, really.
So, Edward sent you in
here to talk to me? Sort of.
Though I can't figure out why
he thinks you'd listen to me.
I mean, you never have before.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Since when are you
and blondie BFFs?
Rose understands what I want.
What are you thinking, Bella?
Seriously.
I know this seems
like a scary thing,
but it's not.
It's like this
miracle or something.
I can feel him.
(SCOFFS)
So, it's a bouncing baby boy.
I'm sorry I didn't know. Should've
brought some blue balloons.
It's just a guess.
When I picture him, I see a boy.
We'll see.
You won't.
Jake, I can do this.
I'm strong enough.
Come on.
You can spout that crap to your
bloodsucker, but you don't fool me.
I can see what that thing's
doing to you. It's a killer, Bella.
You're wrong.
And when you die,
what was the point? Of me
loving you, you loving him.
How is that right for anyone?
Because I sure don't see it.
Listen to me, Bella.
Please.
Just don't do this.
Live, okay?
Please.
Jake, everything's
gonna be okay.
Jacob, don't go.
I know how this ends.
And I'm not
sticking around to watch.
(GROANS)
(GROWLING)
BELLA: Jacob. Jake, I
can do this. I can do this.
JACOB: Don't do this.
BELLA: I'm strong enough.
I'm strong enough.
ROSALIE: This is none
of your business, dog.
BELLA: Jacob, don't go.
JACOB: You did this!
Everything's gonna be okay.
ALICE: The fetus
isn't good for Bella.
JACOB: I know how this ends.
Don't you even care
that it's killing you?
(HOWLING)
(WOLVES SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(GROWLING)
WOLVES: Jake! Jake! Jake!
Jake! Jake! Jake!
PAUL: Is it true, Jacob?
QUIL: What will it be?
PAUL: It's growing fast.
LEAH: It's unnatural.
JARED: Dangerous.
QUIL: Monstrosity.
PAUL: An abomination.
QUIL: On our land.
JARED: We can't allow it.
QUIL: We can't allow it.
PAUL: We can't allow it.
WOLVES: We can't allow it.
SAM: We have to
protect the tribe.
What they've bred won't
be able to control its thirst.
Every human will be in danger.
JARED: We're ready.
LEAH: No time to waste.
JACOB: Now?
SAM: We must destroy
it before it's born.
SETH: You mean, kill Bella?
SAM: Her choice
affects us all.
JACOB: Bella's human.
Our protection applies to her.
LEAH: She's dying anyway!
(BOTH GROWLING)
SAM: We have real
enemies to fight tonight.
JACOB: Tonight?
SAM: You will
fight with us, Jake.
(GROWLING)
(BOTH SNARLING)
JACOB: (STRAINING) I will not.
I am the grandson
of Ephraim Black.
I am the grandson of a chief!
I wasn't born to
follow you, or anyone else.
(GROWLING)
(TWIG SNAPS)
Whoa.
Don't worry.
They're not following us.
What do you think
you're doing here?
I left Sam's pack.
Go home, Seth.
I won't stand behind him.
Oh, yes, you will.
I'm not kidding.
Get out of here.
Is that an order?
Gonna make me bow down, too?
I'm not ordering anyone.
Look, I'm just going off
on my own here, okay?
Great, and I've got your back.
No, you don't.
If Sam comes after Bella,
are you really ready
to fight your own brothers?
Your sister?
If it's the right thing to do.
Whatever.
I'm gonna go give
the Cullens a heads-up.
Do what you want.
How cool is this? Two-man
pack. Two against the world.
You're getting on
my nerves, Seth.
I'll shut up. Can do.
Get ready.
They're coming for Bella.
They're not gonna touch her.
Agreed.
Man, I can smell them
from all the way out here.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm not gonna let my little
brother get himself killed.
Go away, Leah!
I can take care of myself.
That you think so
proves you need a babysitter.
Okay, would
the both of you shut up?
Did Sam send you?
Sam doesn't even know I left.
(WOLVES HOWLING)
I think he just figured it out.
Jake.
I know what his plan is.
Sam's lost
the element of surprise,
and he doesn't want
to take you on outnumbered,
so he's not gonna
come at you head on.
He's got the place surrounded
and he'll wait for his opportunity.
We won't get
through without a fight.
No fights.
We won't be the ones
to break the treaty.
The treaty is void,
at least in Sam's mind.
Not in ours.
Carlisle,
no one's hunted for weeks.
We'll make do.
You've done us
a great service, Jacob.
Thank you.
(WOLVES APPROACHING)
(GROWLING)
I know they're out there somewhere,
but I can't hear them anymore.
It's so quiet.
I stopped hearing them, too,
the second I decided to leave.
It's nice.
You know you can't stay here.
But I don't have any place... I
can't trust you with the Cullens.
You hate them too much.
You don't even like me.
I don't have to.
I just have to follow you.
Look, Seth doesn't want
you here. Neither do I.
Being unwanted isn't exactly
a new thing for me.
Look, I'll stay out of your way.
I'll do whatever you want,
except go back to Sam's pack
and be the pathetic ex-girlfriend
he can't get away from.
You don't know how many times I
wished I could imprint on someone.
Anyone.
Just to break the connection.
(SIGHS)
All right.
I'm gonna do a perimeter run.
You got my flank?
Rosalie, why don't you get
Jacob something from the kitchen?
Thanks, but no thanks.
I'd rather not eat something
with blondie's spit in it.
She would never embarrass
me with such a lack of hospitality.
Hmm.
Of course not.
You'd tell me if she
poisoned it, right?
He broke another
one of her ribs.
(POTS CLATTERING)
Enjoy it, mongrel.
And don't make such
a big deal out of it.
Even normal human babies
have been known to crack ribs.
(LAUGHING)
You got food in my hair.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BABIES CRYING)
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
CARLISLE: Your rib is cracked.
But there are no splinters.
You haven't punctured anything.
Yet.
Edward.
It's breaking her bones now.
It's crushing you
from the inside out.
Carlisle, tell her what
you told me. Tell her.
Carlisle, tell me.
It's all right.
The fetus isn't
compatible with your body.
It's too strong.
It won't allow you to get
the nutrition you need.
It's starving you by the hour.
I can't stop it,
and I can't slow it down.
At this rate, your heart will
give out before you can deliver.
Then I'll hold on as
long as I can, and then...
Bella.
There are some conditions
that even venom can't overcome.
You understand?
I'm sorry.
Edward, I'm sorry.
I can't live without you.
You won't. You're
gonna have a part of me.
He'll need you.
Do you honestly think
that I could love it
or even tolerate
it if it killed you?
It's not his fault.
You have to accept what is.
Because you've
given me no choice!
Bella, we're supposed to
be partners, remember?
But you decided
this on your own.
You've decided to leave me.
Don't see it that way.
Well, I have no
other way to see it.
'Cause it's me who'll lose you.
And I don't choose that.
I don't choose that.
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
COMMENTATOR: Washington
driving in the red zone.
Almost stripped of the ball.
He stood up and Calvin finally...
Are you cold?
I got it.
Don't do that.
What?
Smile like I'm your
favorite person in the world.
You're one of them.
Feels complete when
you're here, Jake.
(BELLA GASPS)
(WHIMPERS)
We need to find a way to
get some food into her system.
If I could only see
the fetus... The baby.
...maybe I could
figure out what it wants.
Think you might be right.
Jacob just had an idea.
It wasn't an idea.
It was a snide comment.
What were you thinking?
That it's probably just looking
for someone to sink its teeth into.
He's thirsty.
I know the feeling.
If it's craving, it's not
gonna want animal blood.
I have some O negative
laid aside for Bella.
Walk with me.
JACOB: Wait, wait, wait.
You're gonna
make her drink that?
It's the fastest way
to test the theory.
Only if you're
comfortable with it.
I'll try anything.
Just hold on.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
This might make it
a little easier to take.
Tastes
good.
Mmm.
Your pulse is
already getting stronger.
It's working.
(DISTANT HOWLING)
Chatty, aren't they?
Just trying to keep us on edge.
It's working.
What?
I can't just stand next to you?
Okay.
See, when I'm close to you, it's
like being able to shut my eyes.
Everything goes away.
Except for the wet dog smell.
Well, I'm glad
I can help someone.
Well, you sound better.
BELLA: I am.
I feel much better.
This whole thing must've put
a kink in the honeymoon, huh?
You could say that.
Otherwise, married
life treating you okay?
Edward still walks
on water and all that?
Yeah, but, I mean,
it is different now.
The important thing
is that you're better.
And that you're
coming home soon, right?
Okay, Dad, I don't
want you to freak out,
but I'm going to a medical
center in Switzerland.
What? No, no, you're not.
You're not going to Switzerland.
What are you...
You said you were better.
I am.
No, Bella.
I'm getting on a plane. No.
No.
It's really more of a spa.
And I'm sure that I'd be better
by the time you got there anyway.
Bells... I don't know.
Dad, don't come.
And picture me healthy,
like I'm sitting on the couch with
you, eating pizza or something.
You want me to visualize?
They say that it helps.
Just picture me like that.
Like I was.
It'll make me feel better.
Dad, I got to go, okay?
Bella.
I love you.
Bella...
(BREATH TREMBLING)
I'm sorry I've been so angry.
(SNIFFLING)
I would be, too.
I've left you alone in this.
Marriage.
Well, they say the
first year is the hardest.
Who was that?
What?
I thought I just heard...
Just say something else.
Like what?
(LAUGHS)
Edward, what's going on?
He likes the sound
of your voice.
You can hear him?
In mind.
He likes my voice as well.
What?
What do you hear?
It's so strange.
I thought he was like me,
but he's not. He's like you.
Good and pure.
He's happy.
Of course you are.
Of course you're happy.
How could you not be?
I love you so much.
What do you hear now?
He loves you, Bella.
Oh, my gosh.
(EDWARD AND BELLA CHUCKLING)
Jacob.
So, that's the last of it?
Bella could deliver
as early as tomorrow.
If she's going to have any chance
at all, she'll need more blood.
And you need to feed.
You have to be at your strongest
for her. We need to go tonight.
Carlisle, you're the enemy now.
Sam won't hesitate.
You will be slaughtered.
Emmett will come with us.
That won't be enough.
CARLISLE:
We have no choice, Jacob.
If there's anything we can
do to save her, we have to try.
You'd risk your lives for her?
Of course we would.
Bella's a part
of our family now.
Yeah.
I can see that.
This really is a family.
As strong as
the one I was born into.
I know what I have to do.
SETH: Jake! They're coming.
I know.
We should phase, Jacob. We
can't protect ourselves like this.
They'll see it as a threat.
I wanna talk!
Be easier if I
could hear you, too.
(SPITS)
This isn't your
territory anymore.
How's the new
family working out?
You done?
You coming home, Jake?
Not until I finish this.
What do you mean?
I want Sam to take
back Leah and Seth.
LEAH: What?
SETH: No way!
Quiet!
I want them safe.
And I want this over.
(GROWLING)
I need Sam to wait until Bella's
been separated from the problem.
You mean till she's dead.
Ease up, Paul.
Then what?
Tell Sam that when the moment
comes, I'll be the one to destroy it.
Jake!
I'm the only one who can.
They trust me.
(RUNNING)
(ESME PANTING)
(GROWLING)
(ESME STRUGGLING)
(EMMETT GRUNTS)
(DOG WHIMPERS)
(HOWLING)
You played us?
Can't we come up with
something just a little more classic?
Thank you.
They make it out all right?
Yeah.
Good.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's not like I'm
the one carrying a demon.
This is pretty important, Bella.
Why don't you tell Jacob
what you've decided?
What now?
Rose is trying to talk Bella
out of her baby names.
She hates them.
Well, then I'm on your side
no matter what you picked.
They're not that bad.
If it's a boy, EJ.
Edward Jacob.
Okay, fine,
that one's not awful.
Why don't you tell
him the girl's name?
I was playing around
with our moms' names.
Renee and Esme.
And I was thinking...
Renesmee.
(LAUGHING)
Too weird?
No, that's not too weird.
It's beautiful.
And it's unique, which
certainly fits the situation.
I like Renesmee.
He likes it.
(GASPS)
EDWARD: Rosalie,
pass the morphine.
(GASPS)
Carlisle said the placenta
must have detached.
(GRUNTS)
He's coming as fast as he
can, but... We'll have to do it.
Rose! Let the morphine spread.
There's no time. He's dying.
Get him out now!
Look at me, Bella.
(BELLA SCREAMING)
JACOB: Rosalie, don't!
(SCALPEL CLATTERS)
Alice, get her out of here!
(EXCLAIMS) Rosalie!
Ow! (SCREAMS)
Save her!
You've got to change her!
I can't, not whilst
he's still in there.
I got to get him out first.
Stay, Bella. Stay focused.
Keep your heart beating.
No! He's suffocating!
(SCREAMING)
EDWARD: Okay.
(LAUGHS)
(BABY CRYING)
EDWARD: Hey.
Hey, hey.
It's Renesmee.
(SIGHING)
You're beautiful.
(GROANS)
(BABY CRIES)
Hey.
JACOB: Bella?
Bella?
Bella!
Jacob, take the baby.
Keep that away from me!
Edward.
I'll take her.
I promise I'm okay. Let me.
What is that?
It's my venom.
(WHISPERING) You're okay.
Come on.
It's supposed to be working.
JACOB: Oh, my God.
Come on.
Bella, come on.
I won't kill you.
That'd be too easy.
You deserve to live with this.
(SOBBING)
She didn't make it.
EDWARD: You're not dead.
You're not dead.
Come on!
No, it will work.
It will work.
Please, please, please, please.
(SCREAMING)
Come back to me, please, baby.
Bella, Bella, please, please.
(BABY COOING)
Hi, hi.
I don't care what he's done.
He's still my son.
I'm sorry, Billy.
I just thought you should know.
Bella's dead.
It killed her.
Let's go!
(SHUSHING)
JACOB: It's like gravity.
Your whole center shifts.
Suddenly, it's not the Earth
holding you here.
You would do anything,
be anything she needs.
A friend, a brother.
A protector.
(WOLVES GROWLING)
Alice! Jasper!
You're gonna be all right.
Stay with Bella.
Do it for him.
Protect him.
We're outnumbered.
By a lot.
I won't let them hurt my family.
(GROWLING)
(ALICE SCREAMS)
(EDWARD GRUNTING)
(JASPER GRUNTS)
(ALICE SCREAMING)
(JASPER GRUNTING)
Stop! It's over!
If you kill her, you kill me.
Jacob imprinted.
They can't hurt her.
Whoever a wolf imprints
on can't be harmed.
It's their most absolute law.
EDWARD:
She shouldn't be this still.
CARLISLE: It's the morphine.
EDWARD: Maybe I was too late.
CARLISLE: No, Edward.
Listen to her heart.
(HEART BEATING SLOWLY)
(HEART BEATING FRANTICALLY)
(HEART BEATING STEADILY)
(HEARTBEAT QUICKENS)
(HEART STOPS BEATING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Ah. It's from Carlisle.
Which is spelt with an "S,"
Sweet Bianca.
He's added a new
member to his coven.
Ah.
Increasing his power.
(BIANCA SCREAMING)
First it's the spelling,
then the grammar.
At least our dispute
with the Cullens is over.
Over?
Mmm.
Goodness, no.
Our dispute goes far beyond
the fate of a mere human.
And what might it be?
Why, brother,
I thought you understood.
They have something I want.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)